#### Contact

Amity University Rajasthan Hostels, Jaipur 8890869618 (Mobile) anirudh80018@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anirudhrana-661918106 (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills Microsoft Office Management Leadership

## **ANIRUDH RANA**

Diving into Machine Learning and Deep Learning | Artificial Intelligence | Techie | Developer

Uttar Pradesh

#### Summary

Engineer in making with industry experience in building Websites, Digital Marketing, and Java packages. I specialize in areas like Data Structures, C++ and WordPress. I also have experience working with Machine Learning Projects and enthusiastically finding relevant opportunities to prove myself. Able to lead others in high-demand situations. Empathic listener and persuasive speaker. Possess an entrepreneurial spirit.

#### Experience

**TCS** 

Project Intern June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months) Lucknow Area, India

Etrainindia Empowening Education Internship Trainee December 2018 - January 2019 (2 months) Delhi Area, India

RECKERS AUTOMATION INDIA PVT LTD

Project Intern June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months) Noida Area, India

### Education

Amity University, Jaipur, Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)

Kendriya Vidyalaya Class 12th, Science · (2014 - 2016)

## Kendriya Vidyalaya

Class 10th, Science · (2013 - 2014)